Guide to the Citizen Soldier records, 1966-2007
Citizen Soldier records, 1966-2007
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Citizen Soldier records, 1966-2007
7033
Citizen Soldier (Organization)
27 cubic ft.
Documents, publications, correspondence, photographs.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes records of the Citizens' Commission of Inquiry on U.S. War Crimes and the Safe Return Amnesty Committee, both Vietnam War-era groups, and a successor of the two organizations, Citizen Soldier.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Citizens' Commission of Inquiry on U.S. War Crimes was an offshoot of the Bertrand Russell Peace Foundation. CCI staff organized the early chapters of Vietnam Veterans Against War (VVAW) in 1970-71. This work is the subject of two books: The Dellums Committee Hearings on War Crimes in Vietnam (Ensign, Rifkin, Uhl, editors, Vintage Book) and Standard Operating Procedure, by James Simon Kunen (Avon Books).
The Safe Return Amnesty Committee worked to win full amnesty for all military resisters to the war, the thousands of men who went AWOL or deserted and were given less-than-honorable discharges. This work is the subject of the book The Amnesty of John David Herndon by James Reston Jr. (McGraw Hill Books).
Citizen Soldier, a successor of the above two groups, has been in existence since 1976. CS has worked largely around issues of concern to active duty GI's, including unions, and has concentrated on veterans' health issues like Agent Orange and radiation exposure. Tod Ensign and Michael Uhl wrote the book GI Guinea Pigs (Playboy Books, 1980), which reports on the U.S. Defoliation program in Indochina and the Open Air A bomb test of the 1940s and '50s and the subsequent perception by veterans that these events have contributed to their decline in health.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Records include organizational records of Citizen Soldier and its predecessor organizations, the Safe Return Amnesty Committee and the Citizens Commission of Inquiry on U.S. War Crimes. Citizens Commission on U.S. War Crimes records, 1969-1974, include correspondence, news articles, publications, sample letters, reports, handouts, legal papers, and military hearings on war crimes in Vietnam and racism in the United States military. Safe Return Amnesty Committee records, 1969-1976, include correspondence, publications, sample letters, newsletters, handouts, press releases, photographs, transcripts of legal proceedings, film scripts, and agendas on amnesty and other national and international political issues of the time. Citizen Soldier records, 1968-1986, include correspondence, news articles, reports, newsletters, handouts, vitae, fundraising information, and letters to the editor on unionizing the military, and health issues, especially Agent Orange, Vietnamese prisons, and prisoners of war.
Also, files relating to legal cases involving military issues including health issues such as Agent Orange, exposure to nuclear testing, exposure to toxic chemicals, drug testing, suicides and deaths in suspicious circumstances, AIDS testing, andother health issues; civil rights issues such as blacks in the military, and gays in the military; military justice including a murder case in Panama, gun smuggling in Grenada, and covert operations; recruiting practices; conscientious objectors; and Vietnam veterans.
Part of Vietnam War Veterans Archives.
Materials relating to the death of Tod Ensign in 2014.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Citizen Soldier (Organization).; Ensign, Tod.; Uhl, Michael.; Citizens Commission of Inquiry on U.S. War Crimes.; Safe Return Amnesty Committee.; Vietnam War Veterans Archives.
Subjects:
Vietnamese Conflict, 1961-1975.; Soldiers.; Veterans.; Agent Orange.; Amnesty.; Prisoners of war--Vietnam.; Nuclear weapons--Testing.; Drug testing.; Gays in military service.; Hazardous substances--Health aspects.; Suicide.; AIDS (Disease); Military law--United States.; Conscientious objectors--United States.
Places:
United States--Armed Forces--Gays.; United States--Armed Forces--Medical care.; United States--Armed Forces--Recruiting, enlistment, etc.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
See also Michael Uhl Papers, #7052.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Incoming and chronological correspondence
Boxes 1-7, 14-19, 23-25, 27
1970
1971
1972
1973
1974
1975
1976
1977
1978
1979
1980
1981
1982
1983
1984
1985
1986
1987
1988
1989
1990
1991
1992
1993
1994
1995
1996
1997
1998
1999
2000
2001
2002
2003
2004
2014
Series II. Organization/Date: Citizens' Commission of Inquiry on U.S. War Crimes, 1970-1971
Boxes 8, 29
War crimes
Racism
Series III. Organization/Date: Safe Return Amnesty Committee, 1971-1975
Boxes 8-11
Amnesty
Political issues
Portugal
Series IV. Organization/Date: Citizen Soldier, 1966-2007
Boxes 11-29
Unions
Health issues
Prison/P.O.W. issues
Organizational files
Agent Orange
Nuclear testing
Toxic chemicals
Drug testing
Death/suicide
AIDS testing
Other health-related issues
Civil rights/blacks in military
Gays in military
Military justice
Recruiting practices
Conscientious objectors
Vietnam veterans
Persian Gulf
Miscellaneous
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Incoming and chronological correspondence
  - 1970
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan.-Mar. (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Apr.-June (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - July-Aug. (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Sept. (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Oct. (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Nov. (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Dec. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Feb. (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Mar. (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Apr. (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - May (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - June (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - July (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Aug. (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Sept. (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Oct. (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Nov. (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Dec. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1971
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Feb. (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
      - Mar. (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Apr. (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - May (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - June (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - July (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Aug. (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Sept. (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Oct. (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Nov. (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Dec. (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - Feb. (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - Mar. (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - Apr. (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - May (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - June (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - July (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Aug. (Box 1, Folder 39)
      - Sept. (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Oct. (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - Nov. (Box 1, Folder 42-43)
      - Dec. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - 1972
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 1, Folder 45-46)
      - Feb. (Box 1, Folder 47-48)
      - Mar. (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - Apr. (Box 1, Folder 50)
      - May (Box 1, Folder 51-52)
      - June (Box 1, Folder 53-54)
      - July (Box 1, Folder 55-56)
      - Aug. (Box 1, Folder 57-58)
      - Sept. (Box 1, Folder 59)
      - Oct. (Box 1, Folder 60)
      - Nov. (Box 1, Folder 61)
      - Dec. (Box 1, Folder 62-63)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 1, Folder 64)
      - Feb. (Box 1, Folder 65)
      - Mar. (Box 1, Folder 66)
      - Apr. (Box 1, Folder 67)
      - May (Box 1, Folder 68)
      - June (Box 1, Folder 69)
      - July (Box 1, Folder 70)
      - Aug. (Box 1, Folder 71)
      - Sept. (Box 1, Folder 72)
      - Oct.-Nov. (Box 1, Folder 73)
      - Dec. (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - 1973
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
      - Feb. (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
      - Mar. (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
      - Apr. (Box 2, Folder 8-10)
      - May (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
      - June (Box 2, Folder 13-15)
      - July (Box 2, Folder 16-18)
      - Aug. (Box 2, Folder 19-21)
      - Sept. (Box 2, Folder 22-24)
      - Oct. (Box 2, Folder 25-28)
      - Nov. (Box 2, Folder 29-35)
      - Dec. (Box 2, Folder 36-38)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Feb. (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Mar. (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Apr. (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - May (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - June (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - July (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Aug. (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Sept. (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Oct. (Box 2, Folder 48)
      - Nov. (Box 2, Folder 49)
      - Dec. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - 1974
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 2, Folder 51-52)
      - Feb. (Box 2, Folder 53-58)
      - Mar. (Box 2, Folder 59-61)
      - Apr. (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - May (Box 3, Folder 2-5)
      - June (Box 3, Folder 6-8)
      - July (Box 3, Folder 9-11)
      - Aug. (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
      - Sept. (Box 3, Folder 15-18)
      - Oct. (Box 3, Folder 19-24)
      - Nov. (Box 3, Folder 25-27)
      - Dec. (Box 3, Folder 28-30)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 3, Folder 31)
      - Feb. (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Mar. (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Apr. (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - May (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - June (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - July (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Aug. (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Sept. (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - Oct. (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Nov. (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Dec. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - 1975
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 3, Folder 43-45)
      - Feb. (Box 3, Folder 46-48)
      - Mar. (Box 3, Folder 49-51)
      - Apr. (Box 3, Folder 52-55)
      - May (Box 3, Folder 56-58)
      - June (Box 3, Folder 59-60)
      - July (Box 3, Folder 61-63)
      - Aug. (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
      - Sept. (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Oct. (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Nov. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Feb. (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Mar. (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Apr. (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - May (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - June (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - July (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Aug. (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Sept. (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Oct. (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Nov. (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Dec. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - 1976
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
      - Feb. (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Mar. (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Apr. (Box 4, Folder 22-23)
      - May (Box 4, Folder 24-25)
      - June (Box 4, Folder 26-28)
      - July (Box 4, Folder 29-31)
      - Aug. (Box 4, Folder 32-34)
      - Sept. (Box 4, Folder 35-37)
      - Oct. (Box 4, Folder 38-41)
      - Nov. (Box 4, Folder 42-44)
      - Dec. (Box 4, Folder 45-47)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 4, Folder 48-49)
      - Feb. (Box 4, Folder 50-51)
      - Mar. (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Apr. (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - May (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - June (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - July (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - Aug. (Box 4, Folder 57-58)
      - Sept. (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - Oct. (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - Nov. (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - Dec. (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - 1977
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 4, Folder 63-65)
      - Feb. (Box 4, Folder 66-67)
      - Mar. (Box 4, Folder 68-69)
      - Apr. (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
      - May (Box 5, Folder 4-6)
      - June (Box 5, Folder 7-9)
      - July (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
      - Aug. (Box 5, Folder 12-14)
      - Sept. (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
      - Oct. (Box 5, Folder 17-18)
      - Nov. (Box 5, Folder 19-20)
      - Dec. (Box 5, Folder 21-23)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Feb. (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Mar. (Box 5, Folder 26)
      - Apr. (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - May (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - June (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - July (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Aug. (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Sept. (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Oct. (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - Nov. (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Dec. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - 1978
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 5, Folder 36-37)
      - Feb. (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Mar. (Box 5, Folder 39-40)
      - Apr. (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - May (Box 5, Folder 42-44)
      - June (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - July (Box 5, Folder 46-47)
      - Aug. (Box 5, Folder 48-50)
      - Sept. (Box 5, Folder 51-52)
      - Oct. (Box 5, Folder 53-55)
      - Nov. (Box 5, Folder 56-58)
      - Dec. (Box 5, Folder 59-60)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 5, Folder 61)
      - Feb. (Box 5, Folder 62)
      - Mar. (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Apr. (Box 5, Folder 64)
      - May (Box 5, Folder 65)
      - June (Box 5, Folder 66)
      - July (Box 5, Folder 67)
      - Aug. (Box 5, Folder 68)
      - Sept. (Box 5, Folder 69)
      - Oct. (Box 5, Folder 70)
      - Nov. (Box 5, Folder 71)
      - Dec. (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - 1979
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 5, Folder 73-75)
      - Feb. (Box 5, Folder 76-77)
      - Mar. (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
      - Apr. (Box 6, Folder 4-6)
      - May (Box 6, Folder 7-10)
      - June (Box 6, Folder 11-13)
      - July (Box 6, Folder 14-16)
      - Aug. (Box 6, Folder 17-19)
      - Sept. (Box 6, Folder 20-22)
      - Oct. (Box 6, Folder 23-27)
      - Nov. (Box 6, Folder 28-29)
      - Dec. (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Feb. (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Mar. (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Apr. (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - May (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - June (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - July (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Aug. (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Sept. (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Oct. (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Nov. (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Dec. (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - 1980
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 6, Folder 43-47)
      - Feb. (Box 6, Folder 48-52)
      - Mar. (Box 6, Folder 53-59)
      - Apr. (Box 6, Folder 60-65)
      - May (Box 6, Folder 66-68)
      - June (Box 6, Folder 69-72)
      - July (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
      - Aug. (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
      - Sept. (Box 7, Folder 7-10)
      - Oct. (Box 7, Folder 11-14)
      - Nov. (Box 7, Folder 15-18)
      - Dec. (Box 7, Folder 19-21)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Feb. (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Mar. (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Apr. (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - May (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - June (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Aug. (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Sept. (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Oct. (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Nov. (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Dec. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 1981
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Feb. (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Mar. (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Apr. (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - May (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - June (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - July (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Aug. (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Sept. (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Oct. (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Nov. (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Dec. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Feb. (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Mar. (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Apr. (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - May (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - June (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - July (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Aug. (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Sept. (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Oct. (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Nov. (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Dec. (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 1982
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Feb. (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Mar. (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Apr. (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - May (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - June (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - July (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Aug. (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Sept. (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Oct. (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Nov. (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Dec. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - Feb. (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - Mar. (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - Apr. (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - May (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - June (Box 7, Folder 50)
      - July (Box 7, Folder 51)
      - Aug. (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - Sept. (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - Oct. (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - Nov. (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Dec. (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - 1983
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Feb. (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Mar. (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Apr. (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - May (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - June (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - July (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Aug. (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Sept. (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Oct. (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Nov. (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Dec. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - Feb.-Mar. (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - Apr. (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - May (Box 7, Folder 58)
      - June (Box 7, Folder 59)
      - July-Aug. (Box 7, Folder 60)
      - Sept. (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - Oct. (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - Nov. (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - Dec. (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - 1984
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Feb. (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Mar. (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Apr. (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - May (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - June (Box 15, Folder 18)
      - July (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Aug. (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Sept. (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Oct. (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Nov. (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Dec. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 7, Folder 65)
      - Feb. (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - May (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - June (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - July (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - Aug. (Box 7, Folder 71)
      - Sept. (Box 7, Folder 72)
      - Oct. (Box 7, Folder 73)
      - Nov. (Box 7, Folder 74)
      - Dec.-Jan. (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - 1985
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Feb. (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Mar. (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Apr. (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - May (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - June (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - July (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Aug. (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Sept. (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Oct. (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Nov. (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Dec. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Feb. (Box 7, Folder 76)
      - Mar. (Box 7, Folder 77)
      - Apr. (Box 7, Folder 78)
      - June-July (Box 7, Folder 79)
      - Aug. (Box 7, Folder 80)
      - Sept. (Box 7, Folder 81)
      - Oct. (Box 7, Folder 82)
      - Nov. (Box 7, Folder 83)
      - Dec. (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - 1986
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Feb. (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Mar. (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Apr. (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - May (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - June (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - July (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Aug. (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Sept. (Box 16, Folder 24-25)
      - Oct. (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Dec. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 21, Folder 33)
      - Mar. (Box 21, Folder 34)
      - Apr. (Box 21, Folder 35)
      - May (Box 21, Folder 36)
      - June (Box 21, Folder 37)
      - July (Box 21, Folder 38)
      - Aug. (Box 21, Folder 39)
      - Sept. (Box 21, Folder 40)
      - Oct. (Box 21, Folder 41)
      - Nov. (Box 21, Folder 42)
      - Dec. (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - 1987
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Feb. (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Mar. (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Apr. (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - May (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - June (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - July (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Aug. (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Sept. (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Oct. (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Nov. (Box 17, Folder 13-14)
      - Dec. (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 21, Folder 44)
      - Feb. (Box 21, Folder 45)
      - Mar. (Box 21, Folder 46)
      - Apr. (Box 21, Folder 47)
      - May (Box 21, Folder 48)
      - June (Box 21, Folder 49)
      - July (Box 21, Folder 50)
      - Aug. (Box 21, Folder 51)
      - Sept. (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Oct. (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Oct.-Nov. (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Dec. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - 1988
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 17, Folder 16-18)
      - Feb. (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Mar. (Box 17, Folder 20-21)
      - Apr. (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - May (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - June (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - June 27, 1988 U.S. Supreme Court: Delbert Boyle vs. United Technologies (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - July (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
      - Aug. (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Sept. (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Oct. (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
      - Nov. (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
      - Dec. (Box 19, Folder 9-11)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Feb. (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Mar. (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Apr. (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - May (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - June (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - July (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Aug. (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - 1989
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Feb. (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Feb. (Box 22, Folder 15-17)
      - Mar. (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
      - Apr. (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - May (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - June (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - July (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Aug. (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Sept. (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Oct. (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Nov. (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Dec. (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 22, Folder 18)
      - Mar. (Box 22, Folder 19)
      - Apr. (Box 22, Folder 20)
      - May (Box 22, Folder 21)
      - June-July (Box 22, Folder 22)
      - Aug.-Sept. (Box 22, Folder 23)
      - Oct. (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Nov. (Box 22, Folder 25)
      - Dec. (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - 1990
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Jan. (Box 22, Folder 27)
      - Feb. (Box 22, Folder 28-29)
      - Mar. (Box 22, Folder 30)
      - Apr. (Box 22, Folder 31)
      - May (Box 22, Folder 32)
      - June (Box 22, Folder 33)
      - July (Box 22, Folder 34)
      - Aug. (Box 22, Folder 35)
      - Sept. (Box 22, Folder 36)
      - Oct. (Box 22, Folder 37)
      - Nov. (Box 22, Folder 38-39)
      - Dec. (Box 22, Folder 40)
      - Misc. (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 22, Folder 41)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - May-June (Box 22, Folder 43)
      - July-Aug. (Box 22, Folder 44)
      - Sept.-Oct. (Box 22, Folder 45)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - 1991
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 22, Folder 47-48)
      - Feb. (Box 22, Folder 49)
      - Mar. (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - March (Box 22, Folder 50)
      - April (Box 22, Folder 51)
      - May (Box 22, Folder 52)
      - June (Box 22, Folder 53)
      - July (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Aug. (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Sept. (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Nov. (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Dec. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - May (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Jun.-Jul. (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Aug.-Sept. (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Oct. (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Nov.-Dec. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - 1992
    - Incoming Correspondence
      - Jan. (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Feb. (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Mar. (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Apr. (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - May (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - June (Box 23, Folder 19)
      - July (Box 23, Folder 20)
      - Aug. (Box 23, Folder 21)
      - Sept. (Box 23, Folder 22)
      - Oct. (Box 23, Folder 23)
      - Nov. (Box 23, Folder 24)
      - Dec. (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Chronological Correspondence
      - Jan.-Feb. (Box 23, Folder 26)
      - Mar.-Apr. (Box 23, Folder 27)